Gordon Kidd Teal papers, Inclusive: 1919-1990, undated, Bulk: 1950-1970, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Professional Work, 1919-1984; 3
  - Professional Work: Correspondence: Texas Academy of Science, 1961 June 5 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Professional Work: Correspondence: Texas Academy of Science, 1961 November 22- 1962 April 28 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Professional Work: Correspondence: Texas Instruments, 1954 March 2- 1961 September 6 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Professional Work: Correspondence: Texas Instruments, 1962 January 10- October 19 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Professional Work: Correspondence: Texas Instruments, 1962 May 15- 1964 September 28 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Professional Work: Correspondence: Washington Award: Pat Haggerty, 1968 April 3-May 1 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Professional Work: Correspondence: Washington Award: Pat Haggerty, 1968 May 4 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Professional Work: Correspondence: Washington Award: Pat Haggerty, 1968 May 15-20 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Professional Work: Diagrams: Bell Telephone Laboratories, 1959, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Professional Work: Directory: Institute of Radio Engineers: Dallas-Fort Worth Members (1 of 2), 1954 December (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Professional Work: Directory: Institute of Radio Engineers: Dallas-Fort Worth Members (2 of 2), 1954 December (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Professional Work: Directory: Texas Academy of Science Membership, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Professional Work: Directory: The Capital Chemist, 1965 September (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Professional Work: Draft: Article: Direction: Gordon Kidd Teal, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Professional Work: Draft: Texas Instruments, Incorporated: “Comments on and Statement of TI General Policy on Research, Development, and Engineering”, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Professional Work: Essay: “Background Memorandum on the Transistor”, 1951 October (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Professional Work: Essay: I.G. Cressell and J.A. Powell: “The Production of High-Quality Germanium Single Crystals:, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Professional Work: Essay: J.A. Becker, C.B. Green, and G.L. Pearson: “Properties and Uses of Thermistors”, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Professional Work: Essay: Gordon Kidd Teal: “How the Next Decade of Electronics Will Affect the Average American”, 1969 November 17 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Professional Work: Essay: Gordon Kidd Teal: “The Role of Materials in the Electronics World of 2012 A.D.”, 1962 May (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Professional Work: Essay: “Some Comments on Certain Aspects of G.K. Teal’s Contribution to Transistor Electronics”, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Professional Work: Essay: “The Chemical Bond”: Part 1, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Professional Work: Essay: “The Chemical Bond”: Part 2, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Professional Work: Essay: “The Chemical Bond”: Part 3 (1 of 4), undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Professional Work: Essay: “The Chemical Bond”: Part 3 (2 of 4), undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Professional Work: Essay: “The Chemical Bond”: Part 3 (3 of 4), undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Professional Work: Essay: “The Chemical Bond”: Part 3 (4 of 4), undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Professional Work: Essay: “The Chemical Bond”: Notes (1 of 3), undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Professional Work: Essay: “The Chemical Bond”: Notes (2 of 3), undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Professional Work: Essay: “The Chemical Bond”: Notes (3 of 3), undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Professional Work: Essay: W. Shockley: “Crystals, Electronics, and Man’s Conquest of Nature”, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Professional Work: Essays: General, 1950 August 15- 1955 December (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Professional Work: Essays: General, 1958-1961 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Professional Work: Essays: General, 1961 March 29- 1968 May (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Professional Work: Essays: General, 1975 January-1984 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Professional Work: Essays: General (1 of 4), undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Professional Work: Essays: General (2 of 4), undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Professional Work: Essays: General (3 of 4), undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Professional Work: Essays: General (4 of 4), undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Professional Work: Financial Documents: Texas Instruments: Five Year Plan, 1958-1962 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Professional Work: Guide: Texas Instruments, Incorporated: Frequently Asked Questions, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Professional Work: Handbook: North Atlantic Treaty Organization, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Professional Work: List: Brown University Alumni: Department of Chemistry, 1936 March 23 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Professional Work: List: Institute of Radio Engineers: Fellows (1 of 2), 1962 July 25 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Professional Work: List: Institute of Radio Engineers: Fellows (2 of 2), 1962 July 25 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Professional Work: List: Invitations: National Institute of Radio Engineers Show, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Professional Work: List: Texas Academy of Science: Ballots, 1958-1961 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Professional Work: List: Texas Academy of Science: Fellows, 1945-1958 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Professional Work: List: Texas Academy of Science: General, 1960, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Professional Work: List: Texas Academy of Science: Members, 1957 October (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Professional Work: List: Texas Academy of Science: Officers, 1949-1961 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Professional Work: List: Texas Academy of Science: Officers, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Professional Work: List: Texas Academy of Science: Officers, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Professional Work: Manuscript: Gordon Kidd Teal: “Single Crystals of Germanium and Silicon- Basic to the Transistor and Integrated Circuit” (1 of 2), 1976 March 15 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Professional Work: Manuscript: Gordon Kidd Teal: “Single Crystals of Germanium and Silicon- Basic to the Transistor and Integrated Circuit” (2 of 2), 1976 March 15 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Professional Work: Memorandum: Taiwan Trip, 1975 May 23 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Professional Work: Memorandum: Texas Instruments: Gordon Kidd Teal: “Proposed Technical Action Plan for TI-International”, 1962 November 23 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Professional Work: Memorandums: Institute of Radio Engineers: Awards Committee, 1958 April 23- 1961 November 22 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Professional Work: Memorandums: Texas Academy of Science, 1953 May 23- 1960 November 18 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Professional Work: Memorandums: Texas Academy of Science, 1960 November 21 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Professional Work: Memorandums: Texas Academy of Science, 1960 November 30- 1961 December 10 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Professional Work: Memorandums: Texas Instruments: General, 1958 July 30- 1960 March 9 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Professional Work: Memorandums: Texas Instruments: General, 1960 April 13- 1961 March 30 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Professional Work: Memorandums: Texas Instruments: General, 1961 May 19- June 22 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Professional Work: Memorandums: Texas Instruments: General, 1961 June 22- July 31 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Professional Work: Memorandums: Texas Instruments: General, 1961 August 30- October 25 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Professional Work: Memorandums: Texas Instruments: General, 1961 November 1- December 11 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Professional Work: Memorandums: Texas Instruments: General, 1961 December 19-29 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Professional Work: Memorandums: Texas Instruments: General, 1962 January 11- April 17 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Professional Work: Memorandums: Texas Instruments: General, 1962 June 8- August 17 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Professional Work: Memorandums: Texas Instruments: General, 1962 September 5- October 19 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Professional Work: Memorandums: Texas Instruments: General, 1962 October 25- November 26 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Professional Work: Memorandums: Texas Instruments: General, 1962 November 28- 1964 August 28 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Council of Scientific Societies: Board of Directors: Gordon Kidd Teal, 1958 May 21- 1959 February 25 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Council of Scientific Societies: Board of Directors: Gordon Kidd Teal, 1959 November 24- 1961 February 9 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Council of Scientific Societies: Board of Directors: Gordon Kidd Teal, 1961 March 16- May 30 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Council of Scientific Societies: Board of Directors: Gordon Kidd Teal, 1961 June 1-13 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Council of Scientific Societies: Board of Directors: Gordon Kidd Teal, 1961 July 31- September 7 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Council of Scientific Societies: Board of Directors: Gordon Kidd Teal, 1961 September 19-November 16 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Council of Scientific Societies: Board of Directors: Gordon Kidd Teal, 1962 January 4 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Council of Scientific Societies: Board of Directors: Gordon Kidd Teal, 1962 January 4- March 1 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Council of Scientific Societies: Board of Directors: Gordon Kidd Teal, 1962 March 5- 1971 May 26 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Earth Sciences Committee: Technical Coordinating Group, 1961 March 2 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Institute of Radio Engineers: Board of Directors, 1958 November 18-19 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Institute of Radio Engineers: Board of Directors, 1959 January 7 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Institute of Radio Engineers: Board of Directors, 1959 May 13 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Institute of Radio Engineers: Board of Directors, 1959 October 8-9 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Institute of Radio Engineers: Executive Committee, 1958 November 17 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Institute of Radio Engineers: Executive Committee, 1958 December 8 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Institute of Radio Engineers: Executive Committee, 1959 February 10 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Institute of Radio Engineers: Executive Committee, 1959 March 30 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Institute of Radio Engineers: Executive Committee, 1959 October 7 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Institute of Radio Engineers: International Convention Committee, 1959 December 8 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Institute of Radio Engineers: International Convention Committee, 1959 December 21- 1960 April 4 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Institute of Radio Engineers: International Convention Committee, 1960 November 29 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Institute of Radio Engineers: International Convention Committee, 1961 January 10 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Institute of Radio Engineers: National Convention Committee, 1959 September 29 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Institute of Radio Engineers: Technical Program Committee (1 of 2), 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Institute of Radio Engineers: Technical Program Committee (2 of 2), 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Texas Academy of Science: Baylor Medical College, 1958 December 12 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Texas Academy of Science: Board of Directors, 1957 December 13- 1958 March 8 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Texas Academy of Science: Board of Directors, 1959 January 21- May 16 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Texas Academy of Science: Board of Directors, 1959 October 5- 1960 April 30 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Texas Academy of Science: Board of Directors, 1960 May 7- December (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Texas Academy of Science: Board of Directors, 1960 December 20- 1962 May 5 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Texas Academy of Science: Board of Science Education, 1957 December 12 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Texas Academy of Science: Board of Science Education, 1958 March 3 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Texas Academy of Science: Board of Science Education, 1958 December 11 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Texas Academy of Science: Board of Science Education, 1959 December 10- 1960 November 26 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Texas Academy of Science: General, 1956 December 14- 1960 September 23 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Texas Academy of Science: General, 1960 November 9 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Professional Work: Minutes: Texas Academy of Science: General, 1960 December 1, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Professional Work: News Bulletins: General, 1972-1979 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Professional Work: News Release: Texas Instruments, Incorporated: “New Transistor Will Shrink Electronic Brains”, 1954 May 10 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Professional Work: News Release: Texas Instruments, Incorporated: “Silicon Transistors in Production!”, 1954 May 10 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “3A Photocell” (1 of 8), 1926-1934 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “3A Photocell” (2 of 8), 1926-1934 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “3A Photocell” (3 of 8), 1926-1934 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “3A Photocell” (4 of 8), 1926-1934 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “3A Photocell” (5 of 8), 1926-1934 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “3A Photocell” (6 of 8), 1926-1934 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “3A Photocell” (7 of 8), 1926-1934 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “3A Photocell” (8 of 8), 1926-1934 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Bibliographies on Photoelectricity and Secondary Emissions” (1 of 11), 1919-1939 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Bibliographies on Photoelectricity and Secondary Emissions” (2 of 11), 1919-1939 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Bibliographies on Photoelectricity and Secondary Emissions” (3 of 11), 1919-1939 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Bibliographies on Photoelectricity and Secondary Emissions” (4 of 11), 1919-1939 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Bibliographies on Photoelectricity and Secondary Emissions” (5 of 11), 1919-1939 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Bibliographies on Photoelectricity and Secondary Emissions” (6 of 11), 1919-1939 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Bibliographies on Photoelectricity and Secondary Emissions” (7 of 11), 1919-1939 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Bibliographies on Photoelectricity and Secondary Emissions” (8 of 11), 1919-1939 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Bibliographies on Photoelectricity and Secondary Emissions” (9 of 11), 1919-1939 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Bibliographies on Photoelectricity and Secondary Emissions” (10 of 11), 1919-1939 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Bibliographies on Photoelectricity and Secondary Emissions” (11 of 11), 1919-1939 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Camera Tubes (1 of 15), 1933-1939 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Camera Tubes (2 of 15), 1933-1939 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Camera Tubes (3 of 15), 1933-1939 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Camera Tubes (4 of 15), 1933-1939 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Camera Tubes (5 of 15), 1933-1939 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Camera Tubes (6 of 15), 1933-1939 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Camera Tubes (7 of 15), 1933-1939 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Camera Tubes (8 of 15), 1933-1939 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Camera Tubes (9 of 15), 1933-1939 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Camera Tubes (10 of 15), 1933-1939 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Camera Tubes (11 of 15), 1933-1939 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Camera Tubes (12 of 15), 1933-1939 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Camera Tubes (13 of 15), 1933-1939 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Camera Tubes (14 of 15), 1933-1939 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Camera Tubes (15 of 15), 1933-1939 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Direction Magazine (1 of 5), 1955-1957 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Direction Magazine (2 of 5), 1955-1957 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Direction Magazine (3 of 5), 1955-1957 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Direction Magazine (4 of 5), 1955-1957 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Direction Magazine (5 of 5), 1955-1957 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “General Files” (1 of 11), 1942-1947 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “General Files” (2 of 11), 1942-1947 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “General Files” (3 of 11), 1942-1947 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “General Files” (4 of 11), 1942-1947 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “General Files” (5 of 11), 1942-1947 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “General Files” (6 of 11), 1942-1947 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “General Files” (7 of 11), 1942-1947 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “General Files” (8 of 11), 1942-1947 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “General Files” (9 of 11), 1942-1947 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “General Files” (10 of 11), 1942-1947 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “General Files” (11 of 11), 1942-1947 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “General Files”: Loose Materials, 1945 May 14- 1948 January 14 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “General Files”: Loose Materials, 1948 February 5- 1949 March 11 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “General Files”: Loose Materials, 1949 May 5- June 29 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “General Files”: Loose Materials, 1949 August 9- 1950 March 2 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “General Files”: Loose Materials, 1950 March 20- 1951 June 4 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “General Files”: Loose Materials, 1951 August 31- 1952 May 27 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “General Files”: Loose Materials, 1952 May 27 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Institute of Radio Engineers Section Editors Meetings” (1 of 4), 1956-1958 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Institute of Radio Engineers Section Editors Meetings” (2 of 4), 1956-1958 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Institute of Radio Engineers Section Editors Meetings” (3 of 4), 1956-1958 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Institute of Radio Engineers Section Editors Meetings” (4 of 4), 1956-1958 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Memos: Gordon Kidd Teal to R.W. Olson (1 of 13), 1958-1960 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Memos: Gordon Kidd Teal to R.W. Olson (2 of 13), 1958-1960 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Memos: Gordon Kidd Teal to R.W. Olson (3 of 13), 1958-1960 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Memos: Gordon Kidd Teal to R.W. Olson (4 of 13), 1958-1960 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Memos: Gordon Kidd Teal to R.W. Olson (5 of 13), 1958-1960 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Memos: Gordon Kidd Teal to R.W. Olson (6 of 13), 1958-1960 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Memos: Gordon Kidd Teal to R.W. Olson (7 of 13), 1958-1960 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Memos: Gordon Kidd Teal to R.W. Olson (8 of 13), 1958-1960 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Memos: Gordon Kidd Teal to R.W. Olson (9 of 13), 1958-1960 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Memos: Gordon Kidd Teal to R.W. Olson (10 of 13), 1958-1960 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Memos: Gordon Kidd Teal to R.W. Olson (11 of 13), 1958-1960 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Memos: Gordon Kidd Teal to R.W. Olson (12 of 13), 1958-1960 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: Memos: Gordon Kidd Teal to R.W. Olson (13 of 13), 1958-1960 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Monthly Progress Reports” (1 of 11), 1931-1941 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Monthly Progress Reports” (2 of 11), 1931-1941 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Monthly Progress Reports” (3 of 11), 1931-1941 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Monthly Progress Reports” (4 of 11), 1931-1941 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Monthly Progress Reports” (5 of 11), 1931-1941 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Monthly Progress Reports” (6 of 11), 1931-1941 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Monthly Progress Reports” (7 of 11), 1931-1941 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Monthly Progress Reports” (8 of 11), 1931-1941 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Monthly Progress Reports” (9 of 11), 1931-1941 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Monthly Progress Reports” (10 of 11), 1931-1941 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Monthly Progress Reports” (11 of 11), 1931-1941 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: “Texas Academy of Science Visiting Scientist Program”, 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: The Raman Effect (1 of 19), 1930-1935 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: The Raman Effect (2 of 19), 1930-1935 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: The Raman Effect (3 of 19), 1930-1935 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: The Raman Effect (4 of 19), 1930-1935 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: The Raman Effect (5 of 19), 1930-1935 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: The Raman Effect (6 of 19), 1930-1935 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: The Raman Effect (7 of 19), 1930-1935 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: The Raman Effect (8 of 19), 1930-1935 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: The Raman Effect (9 of 19), 1930-1935 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: The Raman Effect (10 of 19), 1930-1935 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: The Raman Effect (11 of 19), 1930-1935 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: The Raman Effect (12 of 19), 1930-1935 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: The Raman Effect (13 of 19), 1930-1935 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: The Raman Effect (14 of 19), 1930-1935 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: The Raman Effect (15 of 19), 1930-1935 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: The Raman Effect (16 of 19), 1930-1935 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: The Raman Effect (17 of 19), 1930-1935 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: The Raman Effect (18 of 19), 1930-1935 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Professional Work: Notebook: The Raman Effect (19 of 19), 1930-1935 (Box 10, Folder 32)